I'm going to London
yay London
so I got the opportunity to go to London for a work trip
for a couple of days and I was like
I need to extend this to a full trip
because I haven't been to London since like 20 16
that was back when I studied abroad there
and I feel like it's like another home in a way
and I miss it so much
the city holds like such a special place in my heart
so I'm very very excited to go back
so I'm excited to like for real for real
take you along with me on kind of our first
big trip together I'm excited
are you excited are you excited
let's go pack
I think the first thing I should do is
is check the weather let's do that okay
so it's gonna be like mostly warm
also I'm not a heathen this is a new suitcase
and I'm gonna be washing the sheets
for when my brother comes
to cat sit the cats okay
so all right let's get to packing
gotta have 20 pairs of underwear in case I don't know
somehow pee myself every day of the trip you never know
I'm gonna put my shoes in this one
and then I'm gonna have my toiletries in here as well
shoes
gotta do what you gotta do okay
so then this whole side will just be toiletries
while I'm packing up the last bit of the clothes
I want to talk about two of the pieces I'm bringing
that I'm so excited about
and they're from the brand Quince
and Quince is our cozy sponsor today
thank you Quince
I have been a quince lover for a long
long time
because I got this weighted blanket from Quince
almost a year ago now
the reason that I got it was because I was searching
and researching
for weighted blankets that looked exactly like this
and Quince was the most affordable
like hands down the most affordable on the market
and better reviews and quality
and so I went for it and I'm so glad I did
cause then I got to find out about Quince and finally
finally finally
I got my hands on some of the products
I've been thirsting after
like truly thirsting after
Quince is very well known in the sustainable fashion
communities at this point
because they prioritize sustainability and quality
but still maintain
and affordability that I respect so much
so you can find some nice gold jewelry
you can find cashmere but they're actually like
50 to 80% lower than similar brands
and like we talked about in the decluttering video
I'm really trying to only add
capsule pieces to my wardrobe going forward
that I know I will hold on to for a long time
so Quince
just aligned so perfectly with this season of my life
so this is their boyfriend crew sweater
and it's 100% organic cotton
I don't know if I've ever owned anything
that's 100% organic cotton
and I'm gonna show you the outfit that I plan on
wearing this with I'm so excited
then oh my god
I'm so excited about this one
this is my dream coat
I have been looking for something exactly like this
for months and months and months
it is this like beautiful chocolate leather blazer
and the leather blazers are timeless
like they're in right now
but they're also just timeless
so both of these are absolutely getting packed
for my London trip
so if you wanna make little upgrades to your closet
with Quince go to quince.com/cozyk
for free shipping on your order and 365 day returns
I'll also have the links below for you
but I'm so excited to wear these in London okay
let's finish packing okay y'all
everything is packed it's kind of overflowing a little
I have this whole half open for Ryan if you would like
please don't break please don't break
I love you so much please
ayyy
taking these taking these and this ring
taking these taking these these more dramatic ones
you guys saw the watch and the charm
all the jewelry
I'm gonna bring this one's a great London one
it's very like kinda old school classy
but I don't think I wanna bring it
and then I'm also gonna bring
Glossier oud to just like musk it up
when I need it to be a little more
woodsy musky
but the lineup is Delena, Beach Walk, Rose era, Glossier oud
okay it's my least favorite time which is toiletry time
makeup is getting packed right now
the claw clips are coming
this one's easy cause if there's a pump
oh this is phenomen- oh
you guys that might have been my last straw okay
it's fine everything's fine
professional goop handler
put it on a T-shirt okay
everything's packed in here
the last thing is all my tech so let's go do that
so in my personal I have a whole stash of medicine
I'm the friend that always has medicine if you need it
I have my small wallet
and I have my bigger wallet
that I actually recently found on Mercari secondhand
and I love it it's so cool and I just love it
this little lipstick case
I think it's so cute I got it from Amazon
and it just like holds your little lipstick
and it has a mirror the glossier lipstick
oh I love them
but the cap comes off all the time
so that's why I got this in the first place
I have this um little light up mirror kind of retro style
this pocket mirror and then it also lights up
have this like
purse hooks
so I don't have to put my purse on the ground
when I'm out and about hand sanitizer
I have powdered SPF
two different lip chaps and then I have my glasses
so that's what's in my personal and then of course
like phone charger my passport god
this expires in January of 2025
so I need to renew this immediately
in my my personal carry on
I have my laptop so I can do some editing
portable charges I'm gonna bring two of them
I'm bringing my Polaroid camera
along with a lot of extra film
because of the scrapbooking journey I'm on right now
I totally forgot I had one of these
I have two actually I have one from like high school
and then this is
this is gifted to me in like a just dance PR box
love it and then on my phone
I'm bringing the Moft
tripod that we did a partnership with
a couple vlogs ago
we'll be using this all the time in London
to get some footage for this vlog
so I'm excited for that
my AirPods as well as my little AirPods
it's slightly chaotic but not really
I feel like there's a method to the
to the chaos a little bit
there's definitely a method to madness
and I stand by that okay
I will see you tomorrow when we leave for the airport
I'm so excited okay let's go
I made it I'm so excited
I'm so excited oh my gosh
I love this city so much
and I just forgot what it felt like to be here
and I'm just so excited to be here for a full week
like just driving around
there are some places I remember first of all
I took the underground
it would have been way easier to take a taxi
but I was like I wanna take the underground
I missed it and it was so nice
it was so nice
even with my two like huge bags lugging them with me
it was still so nice to be in the London hustle bustle
and then getting to see like the different stops
I used to take all the time
but now I'm just like settling in
I'm gonna do a little unpacking
today is a day of like
me trying to stay up so that I can adjust to the time
and then tomorrow's just a full day of like
the stuff I'm here for to begin with
with- which is like the content related stuff
Ryan's coming tomorrow and then the rest of the week
we are just living it up in London
it's like a decent hotel too it's like cute
hiiii caption friends!! love y'all!!!
okay y'all I'm back with my smoothie
I missed Argos
I don't know why they don't have Argos in
in the US or like something like it
it's essentially like if a target was only pickup
or like you go to the store
it's just the screens you say I want this
this and this and then they bring it to you like
it's so easy it's so nice
cause sometimes I wanna browse
I love going to target I love browsing
but sometimes just give me the item
you know
like I don't wanna have to see 10 million other things
I just needed the chargers and the hair dryer
and it was like cheap and quick and easy
I also am feeling like so
I don't know I'm feeling not great
I'm feeling like kind of sad and on the verge of tears
and on my to do list
I literally wrote cry on my to do list
and I'm just like
annoyed that I'm feeling sad when I'm like
so happy to be here but oh my God
my point in saying this is that I want to go work out
I had passed by a fitness center
um on the way to the elevator and I wanna go work out
cause I feel like that will help
bring some serotonin to my head
kind of just a lot has been happening
crying is healthy that's why I'm like
letting it out and letting it happen
I'm like feeling the feels
but it's just like frustrates me
cause why now like this is such a happy moment
such a happy time like
but it's okay it's okay
clearly my body needed to do it
clearly I needed to just like physically process
overstimulated in a new place
lack of sleep lack of food period
it's just like time to get emotional
do a little yoga let's go
okay I'm back
patience patience with ourselves
the most important thing we are only human
things can't go perfectly all the time
yay! yay it works
oh my gosh oh
that's the best news ever
that's what I needed right now
computer is on and popping my team is online now
do I wanna do pizza
I just feel like I'm gonna be disappointed
in a Caesar salad and I hate ordering salads
just feel like you can get a
you can make a salad at home
why would you pay money for a salad
unless you know it's a good one
let's take a chance let's take a chance
I'll come back to review the Caesar
I feel so bad I I was in the shower
look
jamming out detangling my hair just like in a trance
did not hear them knocking the door
they called hey
we tried to deliver no one answered I was like
oh my god I'm so sorry
they were like okay
we'll come back
but it's all detangled and now I just need to dry it
okay let's eat here's the salad what do we think
what do we think
okay interesting
it's looking a little milky
but it smells good you know what I do appreciate
they smothered it in dressing
America loves to skimp on the dressing
that's better than a lot of Caesar salads I've had
on the side at a restaurant
I think they're putting real anchovies in
that that's what I'm talking about
that's good stuff
it is currently 5 pm
m I think I'll be working for the next
like five to eight hours ish
and that's really boring
so I'm not gonna show you that
fast forward speedy uppies
good morning it's day 2 in London
and I just did my hair for the shoot
and I have like
all my clothes that I'm bringing laid out
and I'm just gonna head out
yay we're done with the shoot
it was really fun Ryan's here say hi Ryan
Ryan: hiii!
we're gonna do the touristy areas today
so like Covent Garden Leicester Square
here's the fit black linen top from Peppermayo
low waist wide leg jeans
the check shirt from coach Pedro yeah
Abercrombie
Abercrombie Abercrombie Abercrombie um shorts
Adidas gang woowoowoowoowoo
all right we're out
it's day 3 in London and we
babe where are we going today
Ryan: Portobello Market!
Portobello Market but I am pooped from last night
we had like three drinks and we walked around a lot
we walked across the bridge
I don't even know which bridge that was
but we walked across and back pretty
and we're having so much fun here
my face is so hot
burnt?
it's day 4 is it day 4 already?
it's day 4 in London
we're gonna explore the Soho area today
which we're excited about for like shopping purposes
and the fit today we're going cowgirl
you've seen it once you've seen many times again
all Abercrombie Today Abercrombie knitted tank top
Abercrombie denim
Ryan: shorts
Kennedy: JORTS
wish us luck out there
vanilla matcha
vanilla latte
they have the lettuce bowls
how cute then an eggplant dish I want this so bad
they have babe they have like a leaf
look at the platter it's so cute
it's a gaming store and I found Bratz
I found Lego Friends I found Littlest Pet Shop
I found Epic Mickey
which is supposed to be good on Wii
but I never tried it
and I'm still looking through these DS ones
cause I still have my DS and I want to play them
the Sims 2 pets do I have that Cooking Mama I have
do we think Ratatouille is fun
we're home we're back
but that restaurant was so fun
babe what was the restaurant called
Ryan: Circolo Popolare
Kennedy: Circolo Pop-
it was so cool there's like how many bottles five
two hundred?
Ryan: 20,000
20,000???
Ryan: I don't know I might be talking out my ass
20,000 bottles on the wall
these are all the polaroids I just completely wasted
but it took me three times to realize
that's what was happening
in the lens just wasn't opening
cause it was like malfunctioning
three times it took me to realize that
but um we eventually got there
so now we have some cute polaroids
I'm gonna add these to my scrapbook
we got some like food and at the pub some shopping
and then the only thing that I got today
Ryan was the shopper today surprisingly
usually it's me, a bunch of like old games
hell yeah all secondhand
all cheap as hell I am like so excited about this
because whenever I go to secondhand shops
I've been to one in Tokyo
I've been to some in like California
they all are so overpriced
so I appreciate this shop
I'm really excited about that
but that's everything I got
it's day 5 wait
day 5
every day! it's day 5 today we're doing Shoreditch, babe?
Ryan: Shoreditch!
we're doing Shoreditch
and then maybe getting to meet up with mutual
this evening we said this morning
we're gonna have a chiller morning
because we've been going ham right out the gate
every morning and then we're like dying
just like the combo jet lag
and just like movement and heat and stuff so we took
today a little chiller
but also had to finish some work
so it worked out perfectly
also both of us are should I move here
every new place we go let's move here
let's move here why not
I was saying
the only thing I missed last time I was living here
was Taco Bell but they have Taco Bell
but it's not everyone in my community has told me that
it's really bad I used to
say targets but target doesn't light a fire in my soul
the way I used to ya know
let me do lip and then we're good to go okay
all done lipstick is on makeup's done hair's done oh
the outfit babe we didn't do a fit check oh my gosh
a little tube top and then the skirt from cotton on
and then my little Mary Jane's from target
I actually don't remember where the top is from
could be Amazon or TJ Maxx I forget
the fit okay babe
we starting up top?
Ken: yep
dark sport T-shirt again with Abercrombie
Abercrombie military cargoes
Ken: okay
and the Adidas shoes
okay bye
we'll see you out
we're gonna get brunch at Granary Square
yeah watch this space okay bye
okay y'all
it's the last day this the the sixth days Day 6
I didn't vlog at all last night
we were just yapping it up but yeah
we had so much fun
it was Lauren and we took a Polaroid at least
which is really cute
look how cute you'll have to go watch Lauren
if you love the vlogs here
you will love Lauren we had a lot of fun
we had good drinks we had good food
there's this like Ferrero Rocher Martini delicious but I
was up last night I was up
I fell asleep because I was tipsy
and then woke up and then couldn't
we couldn't go back to sleep
but it was delicious it was worth it
we came back home
and we finally went to the pub across the street
that we've been like
looking at every day we're like Castle Hall
we should go to Castle we should go to Castle anyways
today we're going out to Borough Market
we're starting at Borough Market
and then we're going to just like that area of London
so like Sky Garden and then we're meeting Iona
so if you follow any gaming content on YouTube
you know Iona and my streams
cause we've done streams together
we're gonna meet Iona for high tea
little afternoon tea at the Shard
that's that fit check fit check babe you first
new knitted top sleeveless from weekday
just got it here Uniqlo wide fit pleated trousers
loafers from where'd we go Steve Madden
and the pedro bag as always
Ken: lookin great babe
hell yeah
we've got this shirt which I wish was bigger
I just wish it was longer
and not see through
these slacks that I got from TJ Maxx
shout out maxxinista
and then my sambas and then the quince uh
little sweater that I finally can kind of wear
it's been too warm to wear
either the quince sweater or the jacket
the leather jacket burning hot even at night
so finally
I'm wearing as at least like a little accessory
all right we will see you at Borough Market bye
say hi Iona
just trying, trying to muster all the possible energy I have
hey
we're so tired
so we're gonna go down to the hotel steak
there's like a steakhouse at the hotel
we're just gonna do that
and then come back up and watch Love Island
then that's it and then we leave tomorrow
we have to say goodbye tomorrow
I'm getting ahead of myself okay let's go get dinner
look at this bigass
it's like as big as my arm
oh my God
yeah
shrimps
and we got a little Mac and cheese
Ryan: it looks crazy
little waiter boy
we got cheesecake
oh!
Ryan: is it good?
it's really good!
I think the berry is making it
the second to last
Love Island
we're almost caught up although I know who wins
cause I got a spoiler
it's the last day here we're leaving this morning
and I'm so sad we're leaving
but also I feel like we've got a lot out of this trip
I feel like we did pretty much everything we could
we could have possibly done
it was so much fun
did you have fun babe
Ryan: I had a great time
yeah, we had fun
all right I will see you later I love you stay cozy
bye